[{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664030947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":9687,"timeElapsed":56278},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664041603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":10654,"timeElapsed":66933},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664052184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":10580,"timeElapsed":77515},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664057652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5467,"timeElapsed":82983},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664062203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4550,"timeElapsed":87534},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664066108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3904,"timeElapsed":91439},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664069846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3737,"timeElapsed":95177},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664079263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9415,"timeElapsed":104594},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664082496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3232,"timeElapsed":107827},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664094808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10944,"timeElapsed":120139},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664097892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":123223},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664108742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":10849,"timeElapsed":134073},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664111756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3012,"timeElapsed":137087},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664114793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":3036,"timeElapsed":140123},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664117255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2461,"timeElapsed":142586},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664119801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2545,"timeElapsed":145132},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664126322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6519,"timeElapsed":151653},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664129122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2799,"timeElapsed":154453},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664138663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8231,"timeElapsed":163994},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664141045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2380,"timeElapsed":166376},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664147389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6343,"timeElapsed":172720},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664150015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2626,"timeElapsed":175346},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664152886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2870,"timeElapsed":178217},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664154834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1947,"timeElapsed":180165},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664157666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2830,"timeElapsed":182997},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664162627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4960,"timeElapsed":187958},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664164496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1868,"timeElapsed":189827},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664174856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":9355,"timeElapsed":200187},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664177332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2475,"timeElapsed":202663},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664181788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4455,"timeElapsed":207119},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2255,"timeElapsed":209375},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5017,"timeElapsed":214393},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664191608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2545,"timeElapsed":216939},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2199,"timeElapsed":219138},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664199825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6017,"timeElapsed":225156},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664201899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2073,"timeElapsed":227230},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664209652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6924,"timeElapsed":234983},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664214770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5117,"timeElapsed":240101},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664220764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5993,"timeElapsed":246095},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2972,"timeElapsed":249068},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664227436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3698,"timeElapsed":252767},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664229330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1893,"timeElapsed":254661},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664230875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1544,"timeElapsed":256206},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5950,"timeElapsed":262157},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664238837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2010,"timeElapsed":264168},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664243632,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4794,"timeElapsed":268963},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664251413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6943,"timeElapsed":276744},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2564,"timeElapsed":279309},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4058,"timeElapsed":283369},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664262375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4336,"timeElapsed":287706},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3138,"timeElapsed":290845},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664267676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2160,"timeElapsed":293007},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664270041,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2364,"timeElapsed":295372},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664272549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2507,"timeElapsed":297880},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664278201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5651,"timeElapsed":303532},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664279858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1655,"timeElapsed":305189},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664287191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6575,"timeElapsed":312522},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2609,"timeElapsed":315132},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":7611,"timeElapsed":322743},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664299038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1625,"timeElapsed":324369},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3957,"timeElapsed":328327},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1711,"timeElapsed":330039},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2864,"timeElapsed":332904},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664311894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4319,"timeElapsed":337224},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664314370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":339701},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664323150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":7928,"timeElapsed":348481},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664328348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5196,"timeElapsed":353679},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664332007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3658,"timeElapsed":357338},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664335319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3311,"timeElapsed":360650},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3619,"timeElapsed":364270},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664340983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2042,"timeElapsed":366313},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1647,"timeElapsed":367961},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664350841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8209,"timeElapsed":376172},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2325,"timeElapsed":378498},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664363826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9616,"timeElapsed":389157},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1956,"timeElapsed":391114},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664371745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5961,"timeElapsed":397076},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2167,"timeElapsed":399244},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3044,"timeElapsed":402289},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2199,"timeElapsed":404489},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2428,"timeElapsed":406918},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664388173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6584,"timeElapsed":413504},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2325,"timeElapsed":415830},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664397416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5954,"timeElapsed":422747},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4550,"timeElapsed":427298},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664410160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":8191,"timeElapsed":435491},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664413929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3769,"timeElapsed":439260},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664417210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3280,"timeElapsed":442541},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664421202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3991,"timeElapsed":446533},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1647,"timeElapsed":448181},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3926,"timeElapsed":452109},{"subjectID":"xuqy3rsz4b","prolificID":"66c24e9899628532dd846326","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158e04718842243bf7c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2547,"timeElapsed":454657}]